Finding Aid for the J. Warren Perry Collection of Photographs, circa 1910-1971
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Additional Photographs, circa 1910-1971, VIII.; 236 photographs
  - Eleanor Steber as Violetta, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 33, Item C33-016)
  - Eleanor Steber as Manon, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 33, Item C33-017)
  - Eleanor Steber as Vanessa, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 33, Item C33-018)
  - Eleanor Steber as Donna Anna, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 33, Item C33-019)
  - Rise Stevens as Octavian in Rosenkavalier, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bender (Box 33, Item C33-020)
  - Leopold Stokowski, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 33, Item C33-021)
  - Igor Stravinsky, 1953, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 33, Item C33-022)
  - Renata Tebaldi as Tosca, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 33, Item C33-023)
  - Lawrence Tibbett as Renato in Ballo in maschera, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 33, Item C33-024)
  - Richard Tucker as Rodolfo in La Boheme, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 33, Item C33-025)
  - Bruno Walter, 1949, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 33, Item C33-026)
  - Leonard Warren as Baron Scarpia in Tosca, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Seawell, Wallace (Box 33, Item C33-027)
  - Leonard Warren, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Rogers, Houston (Box 33, Item C33-028)
  - Mozart's Geburtshaus in Salzburg, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Baldi & Würthle (Salzburg, Austria) (Box 33, Item C33-029)
  - Drawing of Mozart's Salzburg, with portrait of Mozart, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Behrund, Rud. F (Box 33, Item C33-030)
  - Scene from Mefistofele at the Arena di Verona, 1964, 1964, 1 color photograph; Irifoto (Box 33, Item C33-031)
  - Jessye Norman, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 33, Item C33-032)
  - Kathleen Battle, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C33-033)
  - Dawn Upshaw, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 33, Item C33-034)
  - Postcard of Festspielstadt Bayreuth and Richard Wagner, undated, 1 color photograph; Heilmann, Rudolf (Box 34, Item C34-001)
  - Postcard of the Festspielhaus Bayreuth, undated, 1 color photograph; Oberfräankischer Ansichtskartenverlag Bayreuth (Box 34, Item C34-002)
  - Postcard of Hungarian State Opera House in Budapest, exterior, undated, 1 color photograph; Magyar Távirati Iroda (Budapest, Hungary) (Box 34, Item C34-003)
  - Postcard of Hungarian State Opera House in Budapest, ground floor vestibule, undated, 1 color photograph; Magyar Távirati Iroda (Budapest, Hungary) (Box 34, Item C34-004)
  - Postcard of Hungarian State Opera House in Budapest, staircase, undated, 1 color photograph; Magyar Távirati Iroda (Budapest, Hungary) (Box 34, Item C34-005)
  - Postcard of Hungarian State Opera House in Budapest, first floor lounge, undated, 1 color photograph; Magyar Távirati Iroda (Budapest, Hungary) (Box 34, Item C34-006)
  - Postcard of Hungarian State Opera House in Budapest, interior of hall, undated, 1 color photograph; Magyar Távirati Iroda (Budapest, Hungary) (Box 34, Item C34-007)
  - Postcard of Hungarian State Opera House in Budapest, stage, undated, 1 color photograph; Magyar Távirati Iroda (Budapest, Hungary) (Box 34, Item C34-008)
  - Postcard of Hungarian State Opera House in Budapest, ceiling of hall, undated, 1 color photograph; Magyar Távirati Iroda (Budapest, Hungary) (Box 34, Item C34-009)
  - Postcard of Hungarian State Opera House in Budapest, entrance to the presidential salon, undated, 1 color photograph; Magyar Távirati Iroda (Budapest, Hungary) (Box 34, Item C34-010)
  - Postcard of Hungarian State Opera House in Budapest, entrance to Székely Bertalan Hall and to the presidential box, undated, 1 color photograph; Magyar Távirati Iroda (Budapest, Hungary) (Box 34, Item C34-011)
  - Postcard of Hungarian State Opera House in Budapest, interior of Székely Bertalan Hall, undated, 1 color photograph; Magyar Távirati Iroda (Budapest, Hungary) (Box 34, Item C34-012)
  - Postcard of Teatro Colón, Buenos Aires, Argentina: exterior, undated, 1 color photograph; Edicolor (Buenos Aires, Argentina) (Box 34, Item C34-013)
  - Postcard of Staatsoper Dresden Semperoper, compilation of views, undated, 1 color photograph; Seibt (Dresden, Germany) (Box 34, Item C34-014)
  - Postcard of Staatsoper Dresden Semperoper, exterior at dusk, undated, 1 color photograph; Krull, Dieter (Box 34, Item C34-015)
  - Postcard of Staatsoper Dresden Semperoper, interior of hall, undated, 1 color photograph; Krull, Dieter (Box 34, Item C34-016)
  - Postcard of Staatsoper Dresden Semperoper, stage, undated, 1 color photograph; Krull, Dieter (Box 34, Item C34-017)
  - Postcard of Staatsoper Dresden Semperoper, exterior, undated, 1 color photograph; Krull, Dieter (Box 34, Item C34-018)
  - Postcard of Staatsoper Dresden Semperoper, chandelier, undated, 1 color photograph; Krull, Dieter (Box 34, Item C34-019)
  - Postcard of Staatsoper Dresden Semperoper, Konche der Exedra mit Gemälden von Paul Kiessling Drei Grazien, Apollon, und Marsyas, undated, 1 color photograph; Krull, Dieter (Box 34, Item C34-020)
  - Postcard of Staatsoper Dresden Semperoper, Oberes Vestibül mit Kunstmarmorsäulen, undated, 1 color photograph; Krull, Dieter (Box 34, Item C34-021)
  - Postcard of Staatsoper Dresden Semperoper, Unteres Rundfoyer, undated, 1 color photograph; Krull, Dieter (Box 34, Item C34-022)
  - Postcard of Staatsoper Dresden Semperoper, Zweiarmige Wandleuchte im Oberen Rundfoyer auf Lüftungsgitter montiert, undated, 1 color photograph; Krull, Dieter (Box 34, Item C34-023)
  - Postcard of Staatsoper Dresden Semperoper, Oberes Rundfoyer, undated, 1 color photograph; Krull, Dieter (Box 34, Item C34-024)
  - Postcard of Staatsoper Dresden Semperoper, exterior, undated, 1 color photograph; Krull, Dieter (Box 34, Item C34-025)
  - Postcard of the Richard-Wagner-Museum, Graupa bei Dresden, exterior, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Nowak (Dresden, Germany) (Box 34, Item C34-026)
  - Postcard of the Richard-Wagner-Museum, Graupa bei Dresden, interior, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Nowak (Dresden, Germany) (Box 34, Item C34-027)
  - Postcard of the Richard-Wagner-Museum, Graupa bei Dresden, interior, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Nowak (Dresden, Germany) (Box 34, Item C34-028)
  - Postcard of the Richard-Wagner-Museum, Graupa bei Dresden, interior, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Nowak (Dresden, Germany) (Box 34, Item C34-029)
  - Postcard of the Bolshoi Theater, interior, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 34, Item C34-030)
  - Postcard of the Nationaltheater München, interior, 1963, 1 color photograph; Verlag Fritz Witzig (Box 34, Item C34-031)
  - Postcard of Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, undated, 1 color photograph; Manhattan Post Card Publishing Co. (Box 34, Item C34-032)
  - Pike's Opera House, New York City, 1868, 1868, 1 black and white photograph; Rockwood, George Gardner, 1832-1911 (Box 34, Item C34-033)
  - Postcard portrait of Gioacchino Rossini with titles of his operas, undated, 1 color photograph; Manzoni, M. (artist) (Box 34, Item C34-034)
  - Postcard of Teatro Rossini, exterior, undated, 1 color photograph; Edizioni Cesari (Rimini, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-035)
  - Postcard of Teatro dell'opera, Rome, interior, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Savio, Oscar (Box 34, Item C34-036)
  - Postcard of Terme di Caracalla, Rome, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Vera Fotografia (Box 34, Item C34-037)
  - Postcard of Arena di Verona, three views, undated, 1 color photograph; Edizioni Corsini & F. (Verona, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-038)
  - Postcard of Arena di Verona, undated, 1 color photograph; Piubello Giuliano & C. (Verona, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-039)
  - Postcard of Arena di Verona production of Aida, undated, 1 color photograph; Piubello Giuliano & C. (Verona, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-040)
  - Postcard of Arena di Verona production of La Forza del destino, undated, 1 color photograph; Piubello Giuliano & C. (Verona, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-041)
  - Postcard of Arena di Verona production of Aida, undated, 1 color photograph; Piubello Giuliano & C. (Verona, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-042)
  - Postcard of Arena di Verona production of Carmen, undated, 1 color photograph; Piubello Giuliano & C. (Verona, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-043)
  - Postcard of Arena di Verona production of Boris Godunov, undated, 1 color photograph; Piubello Giuliano & C. (Verona, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-044)
  - Postcard of Arena di Verona production of Turandot, undated, 1 color photograph; Piubello Giuliano & C. (Verona, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-045)
  - Postcard of Arena di Verona production of Lucia di Lammermoor, undated, 1 color photograph; Piubello Giuliano & C. (Verona, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-046)
  - Postcard of Arena di Verona production of Lohengrin, undated, 1 color photograph; Piubello Giuliano & C. (Verona, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-047)
  - Postcard of Arena di Verona production of La Boheme, undated, 1 color photograph; Piubello Giuliano & C. (Verona, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-048)
  - Postcard of Arena di Verona production of La Traviata, undated, 1 color photograph; Piubello Giuliano & C. (Verona, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-049)
  - Postcard of Arena di Verona production of La Gioconda, undated, 1 color photograph; Piubello Giuliano & C. (Verona, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-050)
  - Postcard of Arena di Verona production of Nabucco, undated, 1 color photograph; Piubello Giuliano & C. (Verona, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-051)
  - Postcard of Arena di Verona production of Il Lago dei Cigni, undated, 1 color photograph; Piubello Giuliano & C. (Verona, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-052)
  - Postcard of Arena di Verona production of Un ballo in maschera, undated, 1 color photograph; Piubello Giuliano & C. (Verona, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-053)
  - Postcard of Arena di Verona production of Aida, undated, 1 color photograph; Piubello Giuliano & C. (Verona, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-054)
  - Postcard of Arena di Verona production of Aida, undated, 1 color photograph; Piubello Giuliano & C. (Verona, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-055)
  - Postcard of Arena di Verona, undated, 1 color photograph; Piubello Giuliano & C. (Verona, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-056)
  - Postcard of Arena di Verona, undated, 1 color photograph; Piubello Giuliano & C. (Verona, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-057)
  - Postcard of Arena di Verona, undated, 1 color photograph; Piubello Giuliano & C. (Verona, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-058)
  - Postcard of Teatro Olimpico, Vicenza, interior detail, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Omniafoto (Turin, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-059)
  - Postcard of Teatro Olimpico, proscenium, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Omniafoto (Turin, Italy) (Box 34, Item C34-060)
  - Postcard of the Vienna Opera House, illuminated at night, undated, 1 color photograph; Foto Fayer (Box 34, Item C34-061)
  - Postcard of the Vienna Opera House, exterior, undated, 1 color photograph; Foto Fayer (Box 34, Item C34-062)
  - Postcard of the Vienna Opera House, entrance lobby, undated, 1 color photograph; Foto Fayer (Box 34, Item C34-063)
  - Postcard of the Vienna Opera House, main staircase, undated, 1 color photograph; Foto Fayer (Box 34, Item C34-064)
  - Postcard of the Vienna Opera House, auditorium with iron curtain, undated, 1 color photograph; Foto Fayer (Box 34, Item C34-065)
  - Postcard of the Vienna Opera House, auditorium, undated, 1 color photograph; Foto Fayer (Box 34, Item C34-066)
  - Postcard of the Vienna Opera House, Schwind-foyer, undated, 1 color photograph; Foto Fayer (Box 34, Item C34-067)
  - Postcard of the Vienna Opera House, tea salon, undated, 1 color photograph; Foto Fayer (Box 34, Item C34-068)
  - Postcard of the Vienna Opera House, marble foyer, undated, 1 color photograph; Foto Fayer (Box 34, Item C34-069)
  - Postcard of the Vienna Opera House, tapestry foyer, undated, 1 color photograph; Foto Fayer (Box 34, Item C34-070)
  - Postcard of the Vienna State Opera House, interior with iron curtain, undated, 1 color photograph; Richard Pietsch & Co. (Vienna, Austria) (Box 34, Item C34-071)
  - Postcard of the Vienna State Opera House from the air, undated, 1 color photograph; Alpine Luftbild (Innsbruck, Austria) (Box 34, Item C34-072)
  - Postcard of the German National Theatre, exterior, undated, 1 color photograph; Beyer, Klaus G., 1922- (Box 34, Item C34-073)
  - Postcard of the Hollywood Bowl, undated, 1 color photograph; Thomas, Frank, photographer (Box 34, Item C34-074)
  - Postcard of the Eastman Theatre, Rochester, N.Y., undated, 1 color photograph; Carhart Photo Service (Box 34, Item C34-075)
  - Postcard of the Asolo Theater, Sarasota, Florida, interior, undated, 1 color photograph; Lagerberg, Ted (Box 34, Item C34-076)
  - Licia Albanese as Madame Butterfly, 1940, 1940, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-001)
  - Carlo Bergonzi as Manrico in Il Trovatore, 1960, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 35, Item C35-002)
  - Leonard Bernstein, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-003)
  - Rose Bampton as Leonora in Il Trovatore, 1935, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-004)
  - Rose Bampton as Aida, 1938, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-005)
  - John Brownlee, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Le Boux, Yvonne (Box 35, Item C35-006)
  - Maria Callas, portrait, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Tiffany, Jerry (Box 35, Item C35-007)
  - Maria Callas in rehearsal, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-008)
  - Maria Callas with conductor Antonio Votto, Athens, Aug. 5, 1957, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Harissiadis, D. A (Box 35, Item C35-009)
  - Maria Callas as Norma, 1954?, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-010)
  - Maria Callas as Norma, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-011)
  - Maria Callas as Norma, 1954, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-012)
  - Maria Callas, Nicola Rossi-Lemeni and Mirto Picchi in Norma, 1954, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-013)
  - Maria Callas, Mario Del Monaco, and Cesare Siepi in Norma, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-014)
  - Maria Callas as Norma, Act I, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Wood, Roger (Box 35, Item C35-015)
  - Maria Callas as Imogene in Il pirata, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-016)
  - Maria Callas as Imogene in Il pirata, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-017)
  - Maria Callas as Amina in La sonnambula, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-018)
  - Maria Callas as Amina in La sonnambula, Act I, scene 2a, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-019)
  - Maria Callas as Medea, 1953?, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-020)
  - Maria Callas as Medea, 1953?, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-021)
  - Maria Callas as Medea, 1953?, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-022)
  - Maria Callas as Medea, 1953?, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-023)
  - Maria Callas as Anna Bolena, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-024)
  - Maria Callas as Anna Bolena, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-025)
  - Maria Callas as Anna Bolena, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-026)
  - Maria Callas as Anna Bolena, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-027)
  - Maria Callas as Anna Bolena, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-028)
  - Maria Callas as Lucia in Lucia di Lammermoor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-029)
  - Maria Callas as Lucia in Lucia di Lammermoor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-030)
  - Maria Callas as Lucia in Lucia di Lammermoor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-031)
  - Maria Callas as Lucia in Lucia di Lammermoor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-032)
  - Maria Callas and Giuseppe Di Stefano in Lucia di Lammermoor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-033)
  - Maria Callas as Lucia in Lucia di Lammermoor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-034)
  - Maria Callas as Lucia in Lucia di Lammermoor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-035)
  - Maria Callas, Paul Franke, Thelma Votipka, and Nicola Moscona in Lucia di Lammermoor, 1956?, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 35, Item C35-036)
  - Maria Callas and Ettore Bastianini in Lucia di Lammermoor, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Levi (Florence, Italy) (Box 35, Item C35-037)
  - Maria Callas as Lucia in Lucia di Lammermoor, Act III, scene 1, 1956?, 1 black and white photograph; Lerner, Frank (Box 35, Item C35-038)
  - Maria Callas as Paolina in Poliuto, 1960, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-039)
  - Maria Callas as Paolina in Poliuto, 1960, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-040)
  - Maria Callas as Paolina in Poliuto, 1960, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-041)
  - Maria Callas and Mario del Monaco in Andrea Chenier, 1955?, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-042)
  - Maria Callas as Fedora, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-043)
  - Maria Callas as Alcestis and Paolo Silveri as the High Priest, 1954, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-044)
  - Maria Callas as Alcestis and Renato Gavarini as Admeto, 1954, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-045)
  - Maria Callas as Iphigénie and Dino Dondi as Orestes in Iphigénie en Tauride, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-046)
  - Maria Callas as Iphigénie in Iphigénie en Tauride, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-047)
  - Maria Callas as Cio-Cio-San in Madama Butterfly, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Luxardo, Elio, 1908-1969 (Box 35, Item C35-048)
  - Maria Callas as Tosca, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-049)
  - Maria Callas as Tosca, 1964, 1 black and white photograph; Rogers, Houston (Box 35, Item C35-050)
  - Maria Callas as Tosca, in Act II, 1964, 1 black and white photograph; Rogers, Houston (Box 35, Item C35-051)
  - Maria Callas as Tosca and Renato Cioni as Mario Cavaradossi, Tosca Act I, 1964, 1 black and white photograph; Rogers, Houston (Box 35, Item C35-052)
  - Maria Callas as Tosca and Renato Cioni as Mario Cavaradossi, 1964, 1 black and white photograph; Rogers, Houston (Box 35, Item C35-053)
  - Maria Callas as Tosca and Tito Gobbi as Scarpia, 1964, 1 black and white photograph; Rogers, Houston (Box 35, Item C35-054)
  - Maria Callas as Tosca and Tito Gobbi as Scarpia, Tosca Act III, 1964, 1 black and white photograph; Rogers, Houston (Box 35, Item C35-055)
  - Maria Callas as Tosca and Giuseppe Campora as Mario Cavaradossi, Tosca Act I, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Lerner, Frank (Box 35, Item C35-056)
  - Maria Callas as Rosina in Barber of Seville, 1956, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-057)
  - Maria Callas as Zaida in Il Turco in Italia, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-058)
  - Maria Callas as Amelia in Un ballo in maschera, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-059)
  - Maria Callas as Violetta in Traviata, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-060)
  - Maria Callas as Violetta in Traviata, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-061)
  - Maria Callas as Violetta in Traviata, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-062)
  - Maria Callas as Violetta and Ettore Bastianini as Giorgio Germont in Traviata, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-063)
  - Maria Callas as Violetta in Traviata, Act II, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Rogers, Houston (Box 35, Item C35-064)
  - Maria Callas as Violetta in Traviata, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Rogers, Houston (Box 35, Item C35-065)
  - Maria Callas as Violetta in Traviata, Act III, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Rogers, Houston (Box 35, Item C35-066)
  - Maria Callas as Violetta in Traviata, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Rogers, Houston (Box 35, Item C35-067)
  - Maria Callas as Violetta and Cesare Valletti as Alfredo in Traviata, Act III, 1958?, 1 black and white photograph; Wood, Roger (Box 35, Item C35-068)
  - Maria Callas as Violetta and Cesare Valletti as Alfredo in Traviata, 1958?, 1 black and white photograph; Wood, Roger (Box 35, Item C35-069)
  - Maria Callas as Violetta and Ettore Bastianini as Giorgio Germont in Traviata, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-070)
  - Maria Callas as Violetta and Ettore Bastianini as Giorgio Germont in Traviata, Act II, 1955, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 35, Item C35-071)
  - Maria Callas as Duchess Hélène and Gino Penno as Henri in Les V?pres siciliennes, Act II, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fototeca del Maggio Musicale Fiorentino (Box 35, Item C35-072)
  - Maria Callas, Gino Panno, and Cesare Siepi in Les V?pres siciliennes, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fototeca del Maggio Musicale Fiorentino (Box 35, Item C35-073)
  - Pablo Casals, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-074)
  - Geraldine Farrar with two dachsunds, 1953, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-075)
  - Ferdinand Frantz as Hans Sachs, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-076)
  - Tito Gobbi as Falstaff, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-077)
  - Tito Gobbi as Falstaff, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-078)
  - Margaret Harshaw (as Ulrica in Un Ballo in maschera?), 1948, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-079)
  - Jose Iturbi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-080)
  - Dorothy Kirsten portrait, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-081)
  - Fritz Kreisler, 1948, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-082)
  - Jeanette Macdonald, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-083)
  - Nathan Milstein, 1949, 1 black and white photograph; Bechert, Paul, 1886- (Box 35, Item C35-084)
  - Anna Moffo as Violetta in Traviata, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Reale (Rome, Italy) (Box 35, Item C35-085)
  - Lily Pons, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 35, Item C35-086)
  - Lily Pons, undated, 1 black and white photograph; De Bellis (New York, N.Y.) (Box 35, Item C35-087)
  - Claudia Muzio as Tosca, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Daguerre (Chicago, Ill.) (Box 35, Item C35-088)